Guide to the Serpent's Tail/High Risk Archives ca. 1990-1997 MSS 86 MSS 086
© 2012 Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Author Files
  - Subseries A: High Risk author files
    - Rower, Ann--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 191)
    - Rower, Ann--data, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 192)
    - Rower, Ann--production, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 193)
    - Rower, Ann--publicity, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 194)
    - Rower, Ann--poster (see flat box), undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 194a)
    - Rower, Ann--reviews, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 195)
    - Rower, Ann--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 196)
    - Rose / Texier--contract, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 197)
    - Rose / Texier--correspondence, undated; 31142040616982 (Box 3, Folder 198)
    - Sapphire--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 199)
    - Sapphire--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 200)
    - Sapphire--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 201)
    - Sapphire--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 202)
    - Sapphire--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 203)
    - Sapphire--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 204)
    - Sapphire--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 205)
    - Sapphire--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 206)
    - Shaviro, Steven--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 207)
    - Shaviro, Steven--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 208)
    - Shaviro, Steven--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 209)
    - Shaviro, Steven--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 210)
    - Shaviro, Steven--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 211)
    - Shaviro, Steven--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 212)
    - Smith, Jack--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 213)
    - Smith, Jack--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 214)
    - Smith, Jack--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 215)
    - Smith, Jack--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 216)
    - Smith, Jack--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 217)
    - Stone, Laurie--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 218)
    - Stone, Laurie--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 219)
    - Stone, Laurie--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 220)
    - Tillman, Lynne--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 221)
    - Tillman, Lynne--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 222)
    - Tillman, Lynne--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 223)
    - Tillman, Lynne--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 224)
    - Tillman, Lynne--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 225)
    - Tillman, Lynne--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 226)
    - Tillman, Lynne--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 227)
    - Tillman, Lynne--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 228)
    - Trinidad, David--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 229)
    - Trinidad, David--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 230)
    - Trinidad, David--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 231)
    - Trinidad, David--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 232)
    - Trinidad, David--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 233)
    - Trinidad, David--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 234)
    - Trinidad, David--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 235)
    - Trinidad, David--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 236)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 237)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 238)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 239)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 240)
    - Valenzuela, Luisa--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 241)
    - Weiss, Daniel--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 242)
    - Weiss, Daniel--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 243)
    - Weiss, Daniel--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 244)
    - Weiss, Daniel--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 245)
    - Weiss, Daniel--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 246)
    - Weiss, Daniel--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 247)
    - Weiss, Daniel--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 248)
    - Weiss, Daniel--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 249)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 250)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 251)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 252)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 253)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 254)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 255)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 256)
    - Weissman, Benjamin--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 257)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--appearances / events, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 258)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--contract, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 259)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--correspondence, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 260)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--data, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 261)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--production, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 262)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--publicity, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 263)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--reviews, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 264)
    - Wurlitzer, Rudolph--royalties / subrights, undated; 31142040616990 (Box 4, Folder 265)
  - Subseries B: Serpent's Tail author files
    - Acker, Kathy--Essays, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 266)
    - Agard, John--Loveliness and Mangoes & Bullets, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 267)
    - Amando, Jorge--The War of the Saints, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 268)
    - Andreacchi, Grace--Music for Glass Orchestra, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 269)
    - Atlas Press--general, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 270)
    - Atlas Press--general titles 1995-96, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 271)
    - Atlas Press--Artmann, H.C., The Quest for Dr. U, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 272)
    - Atlas Press--The Automatic Muse, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 273)
    - Atlas Press--Bauer, Wolfgang, The Feverhead, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 274)
    - Atlas Press--Blago Bung, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 275)
    - Atlas Press--Borel, Petrus, Champavert, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 276)
    - Atlas Press--Breton / Elvard, The Immaculate Conception, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 277)
    - Atlas Press--Breton / Soupault, The Magnetic Fields, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 278)
    - Atlas Press--Desnos, Robert, Liberty or Love, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 279)
    - Atlas Press--Encyclopaedia Acephalica, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 280)
    - Atlas Press--Huelsenbeck, Richard, Dada Almanach, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 281)
    - Atlas Press--Huysmans, Joris-Karl, Becalmed, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 282)
    - Atlas Press--Jarry, Alfred, Caesar Antichrist, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 283)
    - Atlas Press--Jarry, Alfred, Days and Nights, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 284)
    - Atlas Press--Jarry, Alfred, Visits of Love, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 285)
    - Atlas Press--Leiris, Michel, Aurora, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 286)
    - Atlas Press--Mangravite, Andrew, The Book of Masks, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 287)
    - Atlas Press--Mathews, Harry, Oulipo Compendium, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 288)
    - Atlas Press--No Bernard, The Castle of Communion, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 289)
    - Atlas Press--Queneau, et. al., Oulipo Laboratory, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 290)
    - Atlas Press--Rigaut / Craven, 4 Dada Suicides, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 291)
    - Atlas Press--Roth, Gerhard, The Autobiography of Albert Einstein, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 292)
    - Atlas Press--Satie, Erik, A Mammal's Notebook, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 293)
    - Atlas Press--Savinio, Alberto, The Lives of the Gods, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 294)
    - Atlas Press--Spoerri, Daniel, Anecdoted Topography of Chance, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 295)
    - Atlas Press--Zurn, Unica, The Man of Jasmine, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 296)
    - Ayrton, Pete--Alphabet Garden, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 297)
    - Ayrton, Pete--Alphabet Garden, reviews, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 298)
    - Banti, Anna--Artemisia, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 299)
    - Baratham, Gopal--A Candle Or the Sun, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 300)
    - Baratham, Gopal--Moonrise, Sunset, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 301)
    - Barrett, Keverne--Unsuitable Arrangements, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 302)
    - Bartlett, Neil-Mr. Clive & Mr. Page, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 303)
    - Bartlett, Neil--Who Was That Man? and Ready To Catch Him, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 304)
    - Belben, Rosalind--Is Beauty Good and Dreaming of Dead People, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 305)
    - Biermann, Pieke--Violetta, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 306)
    - Blincoe, Nicholas--Acid Casuals, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 307)
    - Breakwell, Ian--Seeing In the Dark, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 308)
    - Bruen, Ken--Rilke On Black, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 309)
    - B, Alexandra--This Side of Reality, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 310)
    - Bushell, Agnes--Enumerator, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 311)
    - Caesar, Michael--The Quality of Light, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 312)
    - Caistor, Nick--Columbus= Egg, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 313)
    - Campbell / Rosenthal / Palmer--Back Rubs, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 314)
    - Cannon, Michael--The Borough, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 315)
    - Cannon, Michael--A Conspiracy of Hope, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 316)
    - Capriolo, Paola--Floria Tosca, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 317)
    - Carter / Watney--Taking Liberties, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 318)
    - Cavallo, Diana, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 319)
    - Caveney / Young--Shopping in Space, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 320)
    - Cavazzoni, Ermanno--The Voice of the Moon, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 321)
    - Celati, Gianni--Appearances, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 322)
    - Celati, Gianni--Voices from the Plains, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 323)
    - Charef, Mehdi--Tea in the Harem, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 324)
    - Charyn, Jerome, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 325)
    - Chedid, Andr-The Return to Beirut, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 326)
    - Chirbes, Rafael--Mimoun, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 327)
    - Chomsky, Noam, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 328)
    - Coe, Jonathan, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 329)
    - Collin, Matthew, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 330)
    - Cooper, Dennis, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 331)
    - Cooper, Fiona--Blossom At the Mention of Your Name, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 332)
    - Cooper, Fiona--I Believe in Angels, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 333)
    - Cooper, Fiona--Jay Loves Lucy, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 334)
    - Cooper, Fiona--Rotary Spokes, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 335)
    - Cooper, Fiona--Skyhook in the Midnight Sun, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 336)
    - County, Jayne--Man Enough to Be a Woman, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 337)
    - Coyne, Kevin--The Party Dress, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 338)
    - Coyne, Kevin--Show Business, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 339)
    - Czerniawski, Adam--Scenes from a Disturbed Childhood, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 340)
    - Daeninckx, Didier--Murder in Memoriam, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 341)
    - Daeninckx, Didier--A Very Profitable War (Mask Noir), undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 342)
    - Dale, John--Dark Angel, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 343)
    - De Chirico, Giorgo, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 344)
    - DeLynn, Jane--Don Juan in the Village, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 345)
    - de Souza, Daniel--Under a Crescent Moon, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 346)
    - Dowell, Coleman--White On Black On White, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 347)
    - Duffy, Maureen--Smoke Signals, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 348)
    - Duffy, Stella--Calendar Girl, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 349)
    - Duffy, Stella--Wavewalker, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 350)
    - Duncker, Patricia--Hallucinating Foucault, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 351)
    - Dunn, Suzannah--Darker Days Than Usual, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 352)
    - Durlacher, Gerhard--Drowning, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 353)
    - Durlacher, Gerhard--Stripes in the Sky, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 354)
    - Ehrenburg, Ilya--The Life of the Automobile, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 355)
    - Eltit, Diamela--Sacred Cow, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 356)
    - Etchart, Julio--Forbidden Rainbow, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 357)
    - Fakinou, Eugenia--The Seventh Garment, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 358)
    - Fell, Alison--Mer de Glace, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 359)
    - Fell, Alison--The Pillow Boy of the Lady Onogoro, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 360)
    - Fell, Alison--Serious Hysterics, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 361)
    - Fell, Alison--The Seven Cardinal Virtues, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 362)
    - Fell, Alison--The Seven Deadly Sins, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 363)
    - Fichte, Hubert--Detlev's Imitations, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 364)
    - Fichte, Hubert--The Orphanage, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 365)
    - Figes, Kate--The Best of Cosmopolitan Fiction, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 366)
    - Fried, Erich--Children and Fools, undated; 31142040617006 (Box 5, Folder 367)
    - Gale / King / Wakefield--Secret Lives, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 368)
    - Gardiner, James--A Class Apart, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 369)
    - Gardiner, James-Monty's Private Pictures (gift/photo), undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 370)
    - Gardiner, James--Who's a Pretty Boy Then?, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 371)
    - Gerrard / McCarthy--Passport to Arabia, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 372)
    - Gilroy, Paul--Small Acts, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 373)
    - Glantz, Margo--The Family Tree, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 374)
    - Gordon, Graeme--Bayswater Bodycount, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 375)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--Count Julian, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 376)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--Juan the Landless, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 377)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--Madrid, 1992, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 378)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--Makbara, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 379)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--Marks of Identity, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 380)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--Saracen Chronicles, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 381)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--The Virtues of the Solitary Bird, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 382)
    - Goytisolo, Juan--in Sarajevo, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 383)
    - Graham, Barry--The Book of Man, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 384)
    - Greer, Bonnie--Hanging By Her Teeth, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 385)
    - Hall, Albyn Leah--Deliria, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 386)
    - Haut, Woody--Pulp Culture, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 387)
    - Haut, Woody--Pulp Culture, events, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 388)
    - Haut, Woody--pitch, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 389)
    - Hayward / Lefanu--God, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 390)
    - Hayward / Lefanu--Obsession, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 391)
    - Haywood, Gar Anthony--You Can Die Trying, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 392)
    - Hochschild, Adam--The Unquiet Ghost, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 393)
    - Hopkinson, Amanda--Desires and Disguises, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 394)
    - Hopkinson, Amanda--The Forbidden Rainbow, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 395)
    - Hoskyns, Barney--The Lonely Planet Boy, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 396)
    - Hoyland, John--Bad Sex, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 397)
    - Hoyland, John--Fathers and Sons, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 398)
    - Humann, Klaus--Nightdrive, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 399)
    - Jakubowski, Maxim--London Noir, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 400)
    - James, C.L.R., undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 401)
    - Jelinek, Elfriede--Lust, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 402)
    - Jelinek, Elfriede--The Piano Teacher, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 403)
    - Jelinek, Elfriede--Women As Lovers, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 404)
    - Jelinek, Elfriede--Wonderful, Wonderful Times, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 405)
    - Kharms, Daniil--Incidences, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 406)
    - Kordi, Gohar--An Iranian Odyssey, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 407)
    - Knopf, Marcy--The Sleeper Wakes, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 408)
    - LAB (London Arts Board)--Well Sorted, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 409)
    - Lamba / Ghosh / Payne--Beyond Frontiers, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 410)
    - Langford, Diane, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 411)
    - Lansbury / Korzeniowski, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 412)
    - Larsen, Nella, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 413)
    - Lerner, Jonathan--Caught In a Still Place, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 414)
    - Lerner, Jonathan--Tools of History, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 415)
    - Lewell, John, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 416)
    - Liksom, Rosa--One Night Stands, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 417)
    - Loader, James--Cold Comfort, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 418)
    - Maraini, Dacia--Voices, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 419)
    - Mark, M=--Disorderly Conduct, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 420)
    - Mark, M=--Disorderly Conduct, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 421)
    - Mark, M=--Disorderly Conduct, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 422)
    - Marshall, Paule--Daughters, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 423)
    - Masoliver, Juan Antonio--Origins of Desire, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 424)
    - McCoy, Horace--They Shoot Horses (Midnight Classics), undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 425)
    - Middleton, Christopher--The Walk, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 426)
    - Mildmay, Eroica--Lucker and Tiffany Peel Out, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 427)
    - Moncur, Susan--They Still Shoot Models My Age, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 428)
    - Montalban, Manuel Vazquez--The Angst-Ridden Executive, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 429)
    - Montalban, Manuel Vazquez--Murder In the Central Committee, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 430)
    - Montalban, Manuel Vazquez--Off Side, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 431)
    - Montalban, Manuel Vazquez--An Olympic Death, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 432)
    - Moore, Olive--Fugue, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 433)
    - Moore, Suzanne--Looking for Trouble, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 434)
    - Morch, Dea Trier--The Evening Star, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 435)
    - Mosley, Walter--various titles, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 436)
    - Moyano, Daniel--The Devil's Trill, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 437)
    - Moyano, Daniel--Flight of the Tiger, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 438)
    - Muller, Herta--The Passport, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 439)
    - Nayman, Mich--Jetlag, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 440)
    - Neale, Jonathan--The Laughter of Heroes, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 441)
    - Nuñez Raul--The Lonely Hearts Club, undated; 31142040617014 (Box 6, Folder 442)
    - Oe, Kenzaburo, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 443)
    - Onetti, Juan Carlos--A Brief Life, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 444)
    - Onetti, Juan Carlos--Let the Wind Speak, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 445)
    - Onetti, Juan Carlos--The Shipyard, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 446)
    - Oppenheimer, Josh--Acting on AIDS, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 447)
    - Palandri, Enrico--The Way Back, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 448)
    - Passage to Arabia, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 449)
    - Peake, Tony--Seduction, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 450)
    - Pelecanos, George--Down By the River Where the Dead Men Go, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 451)
    - Pessoa, Fernando--The Book of Disquiet, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 452)
    - Polhemus / Randall--Customized Body, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 453)
    - Printer's Devil, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 454)
    - Pullinger, Kate--appearances / events, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 455)
    - Pullinger, Kate--Border Lines, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 456)
    - Pullinger, Kate--Where Does Kissing End?, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 457)
    - Purdy, James--Malcolm, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 458)
    - Rathbone, Julian--Sand Blind, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 459)
    - Raymond, Derek--The Crust on Its Uppers, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 460)
    - Raymond, Derek--A State of Denmark, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 461)
    - Reaves, Sam--Fear Will Do It, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 462)
    - Reaves, Sam--A Long Cold Fall, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 463)
    - Redstone Diary 1994, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 464)
    - Redstone Diary 1995, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 465)
    - Redstone Diary 1996, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 466)
    - Redstone Diary 1997, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 467)
    - Reynolds, Simon--Blissed Out, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 468)
    - Reynolds / Press--Sex Revolts, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 469)
    - Rodenbach, Georges--Bruges-La-Morte, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 470)
    - Rogers, James--Savage Life, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 471)
    - Romney, Jonathan--Short Orders, undated; 31142040617022 (Box 7, Folder 472)